{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Tuck Pointers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40102/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40102,"taskName":"Brick or Stone - Tuck-pointing","taskDescription":"Brick or Stone Tuck-Pointing","xmTaskDescriptor":"Tuck Pointers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":157,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Brick defective wall walkway walk","textMessagingName":"Brick Tuck-Point","rolloverLongDesc":"Mortar is then placed in the joint \u0026 flushed up. Following this a white line is then superimposed onto the backing \u0026 then cut to a uniform width. Frequently used on restoration work where the joints are defective \u0026 the brick edges have becomes ragged.","rolloverShortDesc":"Replace existing mortar with new mortar \u0026 bonding agent.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Brick or Stone Tuck-Pointing .  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Tuckpointing \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Brick Tuck Pointers","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":16,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Brick or Stone Tuck-Point","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Brick or Stone - Tuck-pointing","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Brick and Stone Project","urlName":"Brick-or-Stone-Tuck-pointing","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Brick Tuck Pointers \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"Brick,defective,wall,walkway,walk,pointing,steps,sidewalks,patio,masonry,out,rake,mason,deteriorated,joints,mortar,Tuck-pointing,Tuck,Point,flooring,floor,Stone,tuckpointing","emcCategoryOid":-12008,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":413,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40102/":{"taskOID":40102,"originalTaskOID":40102,"setID":413,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5219,"questionDisplayText":"Material Needing Tuckpointing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of material needs tuckpointing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5220,"questionDisplayText":"What Needs Tuckpointing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs tuckpointing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Parts of a wall/building","answerDisplayText":"Parts of a wall/building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2240,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Entire wall","answerDisplayText":"Entire wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2235,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Entire building","answerDisplayText":"Entire building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7121,"questionDisplayText":"Repair needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe what needs to be repaired. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1704,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cracks in mortar","answerDisplayText":"Cracks in mortar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1726,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crumbling mortar","answerDisplayText":"Crumbling mortar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3030,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Holes in mortar","answerDisplayText":"Holes in mortar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6590,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Uneven bricks","answerDisplayText":"Uneven bricks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2270,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Evidence of water damage","answerDisplayText":"Evidence of water damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10901,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Need an evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Need an evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5219,"questionDisplayText":"Material Needing Tuckpointing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of material needs tuckpointing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1103,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Brick","answerDisplayText":"Brick","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6094,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Stone","answerDisplayText":"Stone","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5220,"questionDisplayText":"What Needs Tuckpointing","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What needs tuckpointing?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Parts of a wall/building","answerDisplayText":"Parts of a wall/building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2240,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Entire wall","answerDisplayText":"Entire wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2235,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Entire building","answerDisplayText":"Entire building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4593,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Parts of a wall/building","answerDisplayText":"Parts of a wall/building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2240,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Entire wall","answerDisplayText":"Entire wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2235,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Entire building","answerDisplayText":"Entire building","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7121,"questionDisplayText":"Repair needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Describe what needs to be repaired. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1704,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cracks in mortar","answerDisplayText":"Cracks in mortar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1726,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crumbling mortar","answerDisplayText":"Crumbling mortar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3030,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Holes in mortar","answerDisplayText":"Holes in mortar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6590,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Uneven bricks","answerDisplayText":"Uneven bricks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2270,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Evidence of water damage","answerDisplayText":"Evidence of water damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10901,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Need an evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Need an evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1704,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Cracks in mortar","answerDisplayText":"Cracks in mortar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1726,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Crumbling mortar","answerDisplayText":"Crumbling mortar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3030,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Holes in mortar","answerDisplayText":"Holes in mortar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6590,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Uneven bricks","answerDisplayText":"Uneven bricks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2270,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Evidence of water damage","answerDisplayText":"Evidence of water damage","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10901,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Need an evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Need an evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":8,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}